# **Amelia Lewis**

**UI + UX DESIGNER** 

## **ABOUT**

I'm a user interface designer and developer with a passion for design and technology. I love to create beautiful interfaces with great user experience as a top priority.

I have over two years experience working for a digital agency.

#### CONTACT

au +61 422 960 962 us +1 (646) 244-7514 amelialewis01@gmail.com @Amelia\_Lewis amelialewis.com.au au.linkedin.com/in/alewis91

#### **SKILLS**

Responsive UI design UX design Wireframing

Illustrator
Photoshop
After Effects BASIC
InDesign

HTML CSS JS basic

Processing BASIC

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# INTERACTION DESIGNER

**CREATIVE LICENCE DIGITAL • JAN 2013 - CURRENT** 

Creative Licence Digital is a boutique digital agency located in Sydney's Manly Beach. While we're only a small company, we work with a range of big clients, often delivering to users all around the world.

I've been fortunate enough to be able to work across a range of areas over my two years at CLD, including wireframing, content creation, user experience design, art direction, interface design, graphic design and front-end development (mostly web, along with some iOS), with my main focus being in UI design and front-end web development. The majority of projects I work on are hybrid apps, as well as responsive websites and some native iOS apps.

I ve also worked as a...

## **RETAIL SUPERVISOR**

MAX BRENNER CHOCOLATE BAR • APR 2011 - JAN 2013

#### **EVENT WAITER**

BENCHMARQUE • FEB 2012 - FEB 2013

#### PR INTERN

THE WONDERLAND • DEC 2011 - MAR 2012

#### **GOLD CLASS SUPERVISOR**

**EVENT CINEMAS • MAY 2010 - MAR 2011** 

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF DESIGN COMPUTING**

THE UNIVERSITY OF SYDNEY • 2010 - 2012

This relatively new degree was a great introduction into the digital world, covering a range of subjects including interaction design, graphic design, programming, sound design, video editing and animation.

#### **HSC**

KAMBALA GIRLS SCHOOL • 1994 - 2009 ATAR of 95.20

# REFERENCES

#### **ANNIE WILSON**

LEAD DESIGNER AT CLD • +61 481 224 098

# **ABBEY TOWNSEND**

**ACCOUNT MANAGER AT CLD • +61 433 264 749** 

#### **LUKE ROWAN**

SENIOR PRODUCER AT CLD • +1 (917) 704-5355